KELSIE NAKASONE

CONTACT

(805)-231-1288

kkrnakasone@gmail.com

□ knakasone.github.io/

in kelsie-nakasone

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

Computer Engineering Northeastern University 2016 - 2020

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- Java
- HTML5
- CSS3 (SCSS)
- Javascript
- C++
- Python

SOFTWARE

- VS Code
- Visual Studio
- Github/Git
- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Mac, PC, and Linux

PROFILE

Previous IT professional with 2+ years of experience looking to transition into a development and design role. Independently studying and practicing web development by taking online courses and working on personal projects. Combining my technical background and my passion for art and design in web/front-end development.

PROJECTS

Portfolio Website

Jun. 2021 - Present

A clean and dynamic website to showcase my design work and technical skills.

- Developed the site from scratch using HTMl, SCSS, and JavaScript in VSCode
- Styled the site to be responsive and user-friendly for desktop and mobile devices
- Designed the layout, UI, and graphics to create aesthetic web pages in Figma
- Managed the site using organized code, comments, and updates to Github
- Researched how to design, host, and implement the entire site

WORK EXPERIENCE

Helpdesk Analyst

Diamond Game Enterprises | Nov. 2020 - Jun. 2021

Full-time position with the IT team as the first point of contact for all technical support.

- Built a new intranet site using modern SharePoint for the entire company
- Designed and implemented the SharePoint home page for the IT department
- Collaborated with a small team to resolve all IT related issues for 100 employees
- Researched and wrote technical documentation for the team and the company

IT Co-op

Bluewave Solar | Jun. 2019 - Jan. 2020

As a co-op, I spent 6 months during college working full time as an IT administrator.

- Organized tasks in Agile environment with Salesforce to keep track projects
- Provided technical and administrative support for over 100 employees
- Automated laptop provisioning using Windows Autopilot
- Developed powershell scripts to improve the laptop provisioning process